neteller.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy - NETELLER

The Paysafe Group are committed to respecting the personal information of all visitors to all websites managed or published by us, and to ensure that any personal information you provide to us will be stored securely, treated with confidentiality and processed in accordance with data protection legislation and/or any other relevant consumer legislation that is in place to protect you.

All companies within the Paysafe Group adhere to a uniform set of standards that can be found [here](https://www.neteller.com/en/policies/standards).

Individual Websites may have their own privacy policies which are designed to explain in more detail how your personal information will be used for the specific services that they provide.

#### A. Introduction

This Privacy Policy relates to Paysafe Group Plc (“us” “our” or “we”), the Parent Company of the Paysafe Group

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect store and use your personal information when you visit this website. It also describes the types of personal information we collect, and how we use this information to ensure we provide relevant and timely services to you, and to improve your experience of the website. It also sets your rights to the control of our use of this information.

By continuing to use this website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agreed to this Privacy Policy and consent to us using your personal information as described. If you are at all uncertain about any aspect of this Privacy Policy, please contact us using contact details below and refrain from using the website.

#### B. Personal Information

In this Privacy Policy “personal information” means information about you, from which you can be identified, and that can be attributed to you. We will collect, use and disclose your personal information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may collect, use and disclose personal information as authorised by law or with your consent. Depending on the circumstances, your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information may be express or implied. Express consent would arise if you specifically consented to a particular dealing in your personal information. Express consent can be given orally, electronically (by clicking a button) or in writing. If we need to collect, use or disclose any information for any purpose not set out in this Privacy Policy, we will give you appropriate notification and give you the opportunity to object or decline to the collection, use, or disclosure of this information.

#### C. Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. When changed, we will provide notice to you on this website that it has been changed. Please check this website at any time for the most current version of this Privacy Policy.

#### D. Collection of Information

Web Site Traffic Information

We automatically receive the web address of the site that you came from and the IP address of the computer or device that you are using to access our website. We also collect information on which pages of our website you visit while you are on this site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our website. We use this information to try to understand our visitors’ behavior and preferences, to develop and improve our services, and to manage the load on our servers.

Our Use of "Cookies"

We use a number of “cookies” on this site and across all Paysafe Group websites. "Cookies" are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognise if you return to this site using the same computer and browser or visit multiple pages in our site during the same session

For further information about all the cookies we use, [click here](https://www.neteller.com/en/policies/cookies).

To turn off cookies, browsers allow you to do this by changing your browser settings. For further information about how to do this please visit <http://www.aboutcookies.org/> Please note that switching off cookies may restrict your use of this site.

#### E. How We Use Collected Information

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will obtain your explicit or implied consent to use your personal information. Set out below are certain circumstances where we may use your personal information. These are:

  1. To assist us in developing and enhancing our services and our website, to conduct market analysis and strategic planning and to determine your eligibility to receive offers for special features, promotions, and products; and
  2. To provide you with information about our services.

We give access to your personal information only to those employees who require it to provide our services.

Disclosure to Third Parties

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties except in the limited circumstances described below, as permitted by data protection legislation, or with your express permission. These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is shared.

  1. We may disclose your information to assist us in conducting or co-operating in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity where we believe it is reasonable and appropriate to do so.
  2. We may disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or as otherwise required to by law.
  3. We may disclose information to service providers who manage various marketing programs on our behalf. We will only transfer your personal information to service providers that commit to the same principles that we adhere to, and if in another country, we will make sure that the service provider agrees to apply the same levels of data protection as we are required to apply to information held in the EEA.
  4. We may disclose information to carefully selected business partners. 
  5. We may use IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyse trends, administer the site, improve site performance, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and to prevent fraud.
  6. If we amalgamate or merge with or are acquired by another company the successor company would have access to the personal information maintained by Paysafe but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described in Section C.

#### F. Access to Your Information

You have the right to access any personal information that we hold about. Any access request may be subject to a fee (not to exceed £10) towards our costs in providing you with details of the personal information that we hold about you. We may ask you to verify your identity and for more information about your request. To obtain a copy of the personal information that we hold about you please contact us via the details below.

#### G. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy please email [dataprivacy@paysafe.com](mailto:dataprivacy@paysafe.com)

Paysafe is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party referrals, websites or web site links.

This Privacy Policy was last amended on November 9th, 2015
